Rodrigo León - Salesforce Administrator

México/Campeche | LinkedIn | Trailhead | rodrigoleonr@hotmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a Salesforce Certified Professional and Trailhead Ranger with one year of experience in declarative and programmatic development. I enjoy learning continuously and working in multicultural environments.

My Salesforce certifications include Associate, JavaScript Developer I and I am in process to obtain Administrator certification. I have also earned Salesforce Trailhead Superbadges, including Business Administration Specialist, Lightning Experience Reports & Dashboards Specialist, and Lightning Web Components Specialist. You can refer to my complete Trailblaze.me Salesforce Profile, and I would be happy to connect with you at https://trailblazer.me/id/rodrigoleonr.

Prior to starting my career in Salesforce and Web development, I earned a bachelor's degree in Mechanical Engineering and worked for nearly two years as a project manager in the Oil and Gas industry. During this time, I developed soft skills such as assertive communication, teamwork, and attention to detail.

Today, I am passionate about continuing my professional career in the Salesforce Ecosystem and expanding my knowledge of this fascinating industry.

EDUCATION

Universidad Autónoma del Carmen

Bachelor's degree - Mechanical Engineering

Cd del Carmen, Campeche, México

september 2014 - september 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Instituto Tecnológico Ksquare

Full Stack JavaScript Developer

Mérida, Yucatán/Internship

september 2022 - march 2023

6-month online training organized across 1 quarter and two extra months of practice through a real project. Stack: PostgreSQL, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Git

Topre America Corporation | Automotive

Manufacturing Technician

Smyrna, Tennessee, USA/Seasonal

november 2021 - january 2022

- Quality checks on the functionality of parts and components.
- Writing incident reports

Cotemar | Oil & Gas

Cd del Carmen, Campeche, México/Full time

Junior Project Manager

january 2020 - july 2021

- Updating and creating work programs using Microsoft Project
- Preparation of daily project progress reports and presentations.
- Financial analysis of the project using Excel

LANGUAGES & SOFTWARES

Languages: English: B1 | Spanish: Native

Softwares: Salesforce | Microsoft Office | JavaScript